#### Hello

# I'm Stephen Shackleton

4429 Malborough Ave #5 San Diego, CA 92116 (760) 840-0682 shackletron@gmail.com

### **Objective & Skills**

I owned a sign shop in Carlsbad from May of 2015 to July 2022 after working at that location as an employee since 2004. After some post-pandemic struggles I decided to sell the business and seek out a new career path in web development. I am finishing a full stack bootcamp and I'm excited to jump into a new life adventure! I am very hard working, honest and loyal to my employers. I'm a fast learner and can take on new skills and procedures quickly and accurately. I feel that I'd be a great asset to any company and would love an opportunity to prove myself.

## **Experience**

MAY 2015 - JULY 2022

#### Signarama Carlsbad, Carlsbad CA - Owner

- Responsible for all aspects of owning and running a retail sign shop
- Handled graphic design, production & installation, sales, purchasing and point-of-sale
- Grew the company and built a great reputation with my clients

SEPT 2004 - MAY 2015

#### Signarama Encinitas/Carlsbad, Encinitas/Carlsbad CA - Production Manager

- Responsible for graphic design, printing and production of signs and graphics for busy sign shop
- Started with this job as an outside sales rep to cold call businesses and bring in new clients

FEB 2002 - AUG 2004

#### Signarama Oceanside, Oceanside CA - Production Manager

- Responsible for graphic design, printing and production of signs and graphics
- Ran day to day activity of the store for several months when the owner took ill, until he closed the shop in 2004
- Purchased supplies and materials needed to meet orders with my own money when the owner was ill and unreachable for a time, just to keep things going

#### **Education**

AUG 1995 - JUNE 1998

San Jacinto Community College, Houston TX - Associate of Arts

DEC 2022 - MAY 2023

UCSD Ext. Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp, San Diego CA